I have my chicken that we just finished cooking on the stove and it's cooked all the way through.
So we're dealing with cooked rice, cooked chicken and our soap so it's just basically to warm all the way through.
Which we will do in the oven, it's the baking part.
Let's just assemble I'm going to spray down my dish just because it makes me sleep better at night just knowing that it's not going to stick.
Just hold it away from you and give it a good once over and I want to start with the rice, let's put the rice in first.
If you want to put in your chicken first I'm not going to stop you whatever floats your boat, like my dad will say.
Just piling on our rice put all of it, why not, the size of this dish it all depends on if I had more or less rice cooked in this or I have three chicken breast today.
I could of had six or maybe where I had one and I'm just cooking for myself I could of made this a much much smaller pan.
So it's really up to you just as far as to where you have on hand, how much you want to put in there.
Let's get our chicken in next I'm just going to put in there, we'll add in one more chicken breast shove it down in there like a little bed.
All these chicken breast are all so juicy these are great and all we're going to do now is I'm going to break up that rice a little bit.
This would be great maybe if you had leftover white rice from Chinese takeout not the fried rice but you can do stuff with that.
But if you had leftover rice from that how easy is that you didn't even have to cook it and all we're going to do with our soup is just pour it on top and kind of let it all mesh together.